<localeData>
  <EnGB>
    <infectionData>
      <eyes>
        <warning_0>The eye infection is under control for now.</warning_0>
        <warning_25>Eye reached 25% infection!</warning_25>
        <warning_50>Eye reached 50% infection!</warning_50>
        <warning_75>Eye reached 75% infection!</warning_75>
        <warning_100>Brian can barely see!</warning_100>
      </eyes>
      <mouth>
        <warning_0>The mouth infection is under control for now.</warning_0>
        <warning_25>Mouth reached 25% infection!</warning_25>
        <warning_50>Mouth reached 50% infection!</warning_50>
        <warning_75>Mouth reached 75% infection!</warning_75>
        <warning_100>Brian stomach churns!</warning_100>
      </mouth>
      <nose>
        <warning_0>The nose infection is under control for now.</warning_0>
        <warning_25>Nose reached 25% infection!</warning_25>
        <warning_50>Nose reached 50% infection!</warning_50>
        <warning_75>Nose reached 75% infection!</warning_75>
        <warning_100>Brain blobs can barely walk!</warning_100>
      </nose>
      <messages>
        <EYE_INFECT_1>Brian suddenly got pink eye. Gross.</EYE_INFECT_1>
        <MOUTH_INFECT_1>Brian started to feel ill.</MOUTH_INFECT_1>
        <NOSE_INFECT_1>Brian suddenly came down with a flu.</NOSE_INFECT_1>
      </messages>
    </infectionData>
    <menuScreenLevelData>
      <village>
        <speed1>
          <title>A Walk in the Park</title>
          <intro>Thinking to distance yourself further from the bustle of the city, you forgo the lauded rural bus tour in favour of an equally reputed hiking trail suggested by some of the locals. You’ve a good walk to go before you reach it though and you’re not too sure how far it is, so best get some help to find the way, and maybe you’ll find some amiable company!</intro>
          <goodOutro>You’ve reached the end of the trail; a wooded clearing with a few aged stumps and logs laid about. Spotting the prospective furniture one of your companions suggests an impromptu picnic. The others agree with a cheer, retrieving sandwiches, savouries, sweets and serviettes from pockets unknown. What a strange place this countryside is, you think to yourself, but wonderful for it…</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>As your meagre party makes it to the end of the trail, a haphazardly forested clearing with a motley collection of stumps and whatever the bits of toppled trees that aren’t stumps are. You feel mildly disappointed as your companions mill about awkwardly, not sure what to say to one another…</badOutro>
        </speed1>
        <speed2>
          <title>Out For a Jog</title>
          <intro>As your meagre party makes it to the end of the trail, a haphazardly forested clearing with a motley collection of stumps and whatever the bits of toppled trees that aren’t stumps are. You feel mildly disappointed as your companions mill about awkwardly, not sure what to say to one another…</intro>
          <goodOutro>Coming to a full stop you realise you’ve made it all the way to the next town over! You’re not entirely sure if you’ll make it all the way back just now, but before you worry about the return you’re going to explore your new surrounds and see what this happy hamlet has to offer. You turn to the panting crowd around you for suggestions… “Pub?” - “Pub!” …so this is country life!</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>You seem to have come to another small country village, though you’re not sure you’ll have too much luck here; your small party of exhausted joggers has drawn some odd looks from the locals already... Perhaps you should find a bus back or something; they don’t seem overly welcoming… </badOutro>
        </speed2>
        <speed3>
          <title>Revenge of the Grizzly</title>
          <intro>A mid-day hike’s stalled in terrible weather, leaving you sat waiting in the comfort of a cave. You’d been planning to get back once it stopped, but it’s getting dark. You’re not the only thing starting to stir though, and you wish you’d checked further back into the cave. What’s that… a cougar? A bear?!</intro>
          <goodOutro>As you run towards the village you almost fail to hear the revving of an engine and screech of tyres for the deafening screaming following you. A flood of light blinds you, sending the group stumbling from the road. You miss the impact but hear the bear’s terrified roar, turning in time to see a logo emblazoned on the truck’s disappearing rear: “NEIGHBEARHOOD WATCH” – You’re going home.</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>Almost falling over one another as they reach relative civilization, the remaining hikers-turned-bear-escapees lose themselves to panic; pushing and jostling to be first down narrow cobbled streets. The bear pauses, blinking and roaring, unaccustomed to the hamlet’s street lamps, then charges again. Spinning back to run again you find the others have abandoned you… and where was the hotel?</badOutro>
        </speed3>
      </village>
      <western>
        <speed1>
          <title>Farm Hands</title>
          <intro>You’ve got the deed to an old farmhouse outside of town but it’s a bit of a fixer upper, so you’ve come by to pick up some local help. Take a stroll through town and find yourself some prospective farm hands - you’re sure there’ll be someone here to help get things up and running.</intro>
          <goodOutro>Your wife, evidently having heard you and your hired help coming, greets you on your arrival at the ranch. Soon enough she’s to be heard for miles, shouting instructions and ordering the help around the yard. With her lungs you’re sure the work will get done quick, if the men value their hearing.</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>As you approach the ranch a guffaw goes up from your small troupe of curious assistants. “This place? How are y’all gonna get this place running by yourselves?” – they have a point too, you’ve clearly not got much manpower… this could take a while…</badOutro>
        </speed1>
        <speed2>
          <title>Round 'em Up</title>
          <intro>You’ve just had word from the local sheriff: a gang of rustlers made off with fifty of your finest cattle in the night! Luckily his boys managed to drive them off, but now your herd is spread out across the land. Get on your horse and round ‘em up if you want to keep the ranch in business!</intro>
          <goodOutro>You’ve saved the herd, the ranch, and your family’s livelihood! The farm hands cheer as you lead the cattle back to their corral, and soon your family’s come to meet you. Now to get inside - you’ve earned some time off to relax before the real day’s work begins, and after their ordeal you think the cows probably need some too. </goodOutro>
          <badOutro>Returning to the ranch with the few cattle not too stubborn to move, you realise it’s going to be a hard winter with so little of the herd remaining. You’d better get back out there and try to find the rest before coyotes or another band of rustlers finds ‘em - you’d rather search all night than see your family starve. You hear something in the distance… was that a wolf?</badOutro>
        </speed2>
        <speed3>
          <title>Stampede!</title>
          <intro>You’ve been well established for a good while now and this week your wife and children have been away visiting family so the ranch is fully in your hands. Things were looking fine before, but now a storm’s raging overhead and filling the sky with lightning! One bolt’s struck the gate to the corral and now the cattle are loose and terrified – quick, get everyone out of the way of the stampede!</intro>
          <goodOutro>Your flight finished in the safety of the bank, you look around to the incredulous faces of your entire workforce. Suddenly they all give a cheer, amazed to be alive and thankful for it, pledging their loyalty and promising their help in rebuilding the damaged ranch before your family return home! </goodOutro>
          <badOutro>Huddled together in the bank vault as the cattle still roam outside, your workers turn to questioning how the cattle escaped in the storm. You try to explain you saw the lightning strike the gate, but they’re having none of it. “As soon as those demon cows are out of here, so are we!”</badOutro>
        </speed3>
      </western>
      <medieval>
        <speed1>
          <title>Cash King</title>
          <intro>The king has sent out a proclamation across the lands. His master of coffers has been coughing introretely and the royal vaults are wanting for coin. By royal decree you and your peasant brethren are required to provide the kingdom's funds in greater than ever supply. Unfortunately, as a bunch of freeholding farmers, you don't have any gold. Lead the people to petition the crown for reprieve.</intro>
          <goodOutro>A throbbing mob of sweaty, shouting peasants arrayed before him, the King is overawed and dismayed by the support you have gathered, and more than a little fearful for his furnishings with the mud you’ve tracked in. Eager to see your backs he offers you another option: to pay him off with a grand feast. Fail though, and he’ll lock you in and feed you to his prized hounds.</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>“You paltry bunch of pissants think to challenge MY lawful dictates? GUARDS! Dangle these dissenters from the walls! And when the other bits have fallen off, stick their heads above the gate! Maybe the next batch of stinking vermin will think twice before saying no to their King!”</badOutro>
        </speed1>
        <speed2>
          <title>Feast for a King</title>
          <intro>Your plea successul, the King has relented, requiring instead that you feat him and his hounds, lest he bar the doors of his hall with you inside and loose them to feast upon you. Get your haste on and gather the townsfolk and their wares to the royal kitchens, and make sure not to forget the salt!</intro>
          <goodOutro>Platters of roasted meats and steaming stews fill the King’s great hall with the smell of the feast. The village watches on from the shadows as the nobles try each dish, the King himself wordless as he tries and tests each bite, weighing its worth in gold. Eventually he drops his cutlery with a clatter, silencing his table guests. “Unbar the doors…” he says, “they may leave with their lives.”</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>Too many cooks can apparently spoil the metaphorical broth, but with the effort that was required for this culinary challenge perhaps you should have gathered a few more… The nobles at table are muttering their displeasure and the King is still staring into his meal. Is that a fish knife? You don’t remember preparing any – oh. Oh dear.</badOutro>
        </speed2>
        <speed3>
          <title>Hounded</title>
          <intro>His meal seemingly satisfactory, the King honours his oath - the part about not barring the doors on the townsfolk at least - "Now flee for your lives, petty peasants!" he cries, unleashing his dogs from the throne with a depraved grin. Run fast, run far, save as many villagers as you can and don't trip - the hounds are swift, and their jaws are almost as cruel as their master.</intro>
          <goodOutro>You might not be sure how, but near all of the villagers made it. Panting and shaking from their ordeal they gather together to thank you, their saviour. A day may come when you once again have to run from that despicable despot, but at least you’ll live to see it. If you’re lucky you’ll be left in peace – the King seems little like the type to expect your miraculous survival. Well done indeed!</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>The baying of the hounds still echoing in your ears, your few fellow survivors collapse around you as terror gives way to despair. You can only hope that some of the others may have found their own escape, but the screams weigh almost as heavy upon you as the gaze of those who survived. Curse the King, his greed, and his malice, but the village will curse the man who led them to their misery. </badOutro>
        </speed3>
      </medieval>
      <egypt>
        <speed1>
          <title>Laying the Foundations</title>
          <intro>Somehow you've received the ultimate commission from the Pharaoh himself, but as ever the boss is nowhere to be found! Round up the workers and get searching for a spot, and you might even get credit for laying the greatest foundations in history!</intro>
          <goodOutro>After a thorough search you’ve found the perfect location for the Pharaoh’s great testament to his own divine rule, and you’ve even got the manpower ready to start laying out some groundwork! Surely no one would notice if a few walls on the bottom layer just happened to spell out your name in hieroglyphs right?</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>You’ve found the perfect spot, but you haven’t the manpower to start working! Someone’s going to have to go back and seek out the boss, and you know as soon as he’s here he’ll claim the find as his own. Oh well, if the world never knows your name, at least it’ll still marvel at your efforts.</badOutro>
        </speed1>
        <speed2>
          <title>Looking Busy</title>
          <intro>Construction's underway and, sick of fulfilling his responsibilities, the master's decreed a day of rest. Unfortunately you've just had word of an imminent visitor. Not just a royal inspector, but the Pharaoh himself! Round up the workers, lash them if must, but don't let him see an empty yard!</intro>
          <goodOutro>You’re sure it won’t last long but for now the workers are back to the toil and at least looking busy in silence for the duration of their great ruler’s visit.  The Pharaoh looks pleased with the work you’ve managed so far, even mistaking you for the master architect himself! Of course, that means your boss will yet again be claiming the credit, and without even having been here, but it beats whipping!</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>With little enough of the workforce there, you decide to improvise, claiming they were removed for being unworthy of the Pharaoh’s presence. Instead you begin to show his greatness around his grand pyramid. By the time you’ve demonstrated all four sides however he’s grown bored, and decides to try his divine hand at foremaning; having a bodyguard whip you constantly as you toil. </badOutro>
        </speed2>
        <speed3>
          <title>Shifting Sands</title>
          <intro>The majestic monument complete, the master foreman takes it upon himself to place the tiny golden capstone. Unfortunately as he nears the top, the sands at the base begin to shift, pouring inwards...disaster! The monument is sinking! Get away and warn the workers before it's too late!</intro>
          <goodOutro>Finally escaping the pull of the sinking pyramid you turn, panting with relief. All that remains above the sands is a golden glint, the very tip of the capstone, and around it… is that the master’s hand? You start towards it but a worker pulls you back. “He is lost, let this disaster’s blame go with him. You’re the foreman now – this is your chance to put your name to the Pharaoh’s next triumph.”</goodOutro>
          <badOutro>Finally escaping the pull of the sinking pyramid you turn, panting with relief. All that remains above the sands is a golden glint, the very tip of the capstone, and around it… is that the master’s hand? The sands now stilled, you rush towards him. There’s still movement! Dragging him out takes more than a little help, but you succeed! For the first time in your life, he thanks you. By the wrong name…</badOutro>
        </speed3>
      </egypt>
    </menuScreenLevelData>
  </EnGB>
</localeData>
